[
  {
    "question": "What is an Ocean?",
    "optionOne": "A large body of salted water.",
    "optionTwo": "A large sea.",
    "optionThree": "A large lake.",
    "correctAnswer": "A large body of salted water."
  },
  {
    "question": "How much of the Earth surface is covered by the ocean?",
    "optionOne": "About 30%.",
    "optionTwo": "About 50%.",
    "optionThree": "About 70%.",
    "correctAnswer": "About 70%."
  },
  {
    "question": "Nowadays how many oceans exist?",
    "optionOne": "4.",
    "optionTwo": "5.",
    "optionThree": "6.",
    "correctAnswer": "5."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not an ocean?",
    "optionOne": "Pacific.",
    "optionTwo": "Indian.",
    "optionThree": "American.",
    "correctAnswer": "American."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is called the zone defined by the tidal range?",
    "optionOne": "Intertidal zone.",
    "optionTwo": "Midtidal zone.",
    "optionThree": "Ecotidal zone.",
    "correctAnswer": "Intertidal zone."
  },
  {
    "question": "How much oxygen is produced by the ocean?",
    "optionOne": "About 20%.",
    "optionTwo": "About 50%.",
    "optionThree": "About 70%.",
    "correctAnswer": "About 50%."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following facts is false?",
    "optionOne": "More than 80% of the ocean is unexplored.",
    "optionTwo": "Water takes about 1000 years to travel all the way around the globe.",
    "optionThree": "Less than 60% of the total water on Earth is in the Ocean.",
    "correctAnswer": "Less than 60% of the total water on Earth is in the Ocean."
  },
  {
    "question": "Wich is the largest ocean?",
    "optionOne": "Pacific.",
    "optionTwo": "Antartic.",
    "optionThree": "Atlantic.",
    "correctAnswer": "Pacific."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is oceanology?",
    "optionOne": "The study of Earth surface.",
    "optionTwo": "The study of the ocean.",
    "optionThree": "Whom study the ocean.",
    "correctAnswer": "The study of the ocean."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the folling is not plankton?",
    "optionOne": "Phytoplankton.",
    "optionTwo": "Zooplankton.",
    "optionThree": "Oceoplankton.",
    "correctAnswer": "Oceoplankton."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is evaporation?",
    "optionOne": "Water changing state from liquid to vapor.",
    "optionTwo": "Water changing state from solid to liquid.",
    "optionThree": "Water changing state from solid to vapor.",
    "correctAnswer": "Water changing state from liquid to vapor."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the oceans is the warmest?",
    "optionOne": "Pacific.",
    "optionTwo": "Indian.",
    "optionThree": "Atlantic.",
    "correctAnswer": "Indian."
  }
]